(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)All right, team,
open up your practice kits.
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)As the university did not permit me
to bring the equipment we'll be using...
(Sheldon:)...to the Cheesecake Factory,
because apparently, I'm ridiculous...
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)...I've provided substitutes
which will exercise your fine motor skills.
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)Leonard, you will be doing a series
of complex mathematical problems...
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)...on a vintage Casio model 1175
calculator watch I received...
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)...when I won the Earth Science medal
in third grade.
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)Treat it with respect.
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)Raj, you will be painting sideburns
and a Vandyke...
...on a 6-inch figurine
of Legolas the Elf.
Now, remember, a Vandyke
is a goatee without a mustache.
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)Wolowitz, you will be completing a series
of delicate surgical procedures...
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)...on the classic children's game,
Operation.
(Sheldon(pointing at his brain):)To begin with,
you will remove funny bone for $200.